[{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980474682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":13750,"timeElapsed":36516},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980482121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":7437,"timeElapsed":43954},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980490116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7994,"timeElapsed":51950},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980523902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":33784,"timeElapsed":85736},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980527194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":3291,"timeElapsed":89028},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980530995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3799,"timeElapsed":92829},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980533353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2357,"timeElapsed":95187},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":8569,"timeElapsed":103757},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980545830,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3906,"timeElapsed":107664},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980552329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":5410,"timeElapsed":114163},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980554737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2407,"timeElapsed":116571},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980561458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6719,"timeElapsed":123291},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980564004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2546,"timeElapsed":125838},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2243,"timeElapsed":128082},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2137,"timeElapsed":130220},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570638,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2251,"timeElapsed":132472},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980642967,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":72328,"timeElapsed":204801},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980645202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2234,"timeElapsed":207036},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980651933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":4920,"timeElapsed":213767},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980654005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2071,"timeElapsed":215839},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980657419,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3413,"timeElapsed":219253},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980659738,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2318,"timeElapsed":221572},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980663152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":3413,"timeElapsed":224986},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980665142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1989,"timeElapsed":226976},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980667362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2219,"timeElapsed":229195},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980670572,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3210,"timeElapsed":232406},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980673389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2816,"timeElapsed":235223},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980680180,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6789,"timeElapsed":242013},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980691562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":10465,"timeElapsed":253395},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980693363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":1801,"timeElapsed":255197},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980697335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3971,"timeElapsed":259169},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980699636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2300,"timeElapsed":261470},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980701905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2268,"timeElapsed":263739},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980704042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2136,"timeElapsed":265876},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980706426,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2383,"timeElapsed":268260},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980709488,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3061,"timeElapsed":271322},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980711388,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1899,"timeElapsed":273222},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980719140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":6613,"timeElapsed":280974},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980721621,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2481,"timeElapsed":283455},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980840394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":118772,"timeElapsed":402228},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980842678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2283,"timeElapsed":404512},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980845234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2555,"timeElapsed":407068},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980847740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2504,"timeElapsed":409574},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980849730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1989,"timeElapsed":411564},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980854513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4782,"timeElapsed":416347},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980857363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"22","question":"Describe three to five positive characteristics of your closest friend or partner.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2849,"timeElapsed":419197},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980866825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":8552,"timeElapsed":428659},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980868397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1571,"timeElapsed":430231},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980870756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2358,"timeElapsed":432590},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980872647,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1890,"timeElapsed":434481},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980875563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2915,"timeElapsed":437397},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980878347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2783,"timeElapsed":440181},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980882024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3676,"timeElapsed":443858},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980884767,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2742,"timeElapsed":446601},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980887593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2824,"timeElapsed":449427},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980894662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":6111,"timeElapsed":456496},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980896768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2104,"timeElapsed":458602},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980899610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2841,"timeElapsed":461444},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980901820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2209,"timeElapsed":463654},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980903769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1948,"timeElapsed":465603},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980905890,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2120,"timeElapsed":467724},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980907733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1842,"timeElapsed":469567},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980910780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3046,"timeElapsed":472614},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980915153,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4370,"timeElapsed":476987},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980920600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4643,"timeElapsed":482433},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980922343,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1743,"timeElapsed":484177},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980925349,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3005,"timeElapsed":487183},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980927872,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2522,"timeElapsed":489705},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980930074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2202,"timeElapsed":491908},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980932031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1956,"timeElapsed":493865},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980936571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4539,"timeElapsed":498405},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980947588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":11016,"timeElapsed":509422},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980953967,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6378,"timeElapsed":515801},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980956703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2734,"timeElapsed":518537},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980960863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3372,"timeElapsed":522697},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980962820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1956,"timeElapsed":524654},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980965129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2308,"timeElapsed":526963},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980966956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1826,"timeElapsed":528790},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980968855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1898,"timeElapsed":530689},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980972269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3414,"timeElapsed":534103},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980978561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6291,"timeElapsed":540395},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980980904,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2341,"timeElapsed":542738},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980982910,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2005,"timeElapsed":544743},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980987291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3554,"timeElapsed":549125},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980989035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1743,"timeElapsed":550869},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980991001,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1965,"timeElapsed":552834},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980993514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2513,"timeElapsed":555348},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980995718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2203,"timeElapsed":557552},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980997773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2055,"timeElapsed":559607},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980999730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1956,"timeElapsed":561564},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981002596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2865,"timeElapsed":564430},{"subjectID":"dxflk7r1uv","prolificID":"66ff353752eb0274c34253fe","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b268246a4cfbd06c4a83","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981004366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1768,"timeElapsed":566199}]